The army of the four generals in flames
This will be the last battle.
Take your seat when Suzuki Moe! One swing game!
During the battle
Just do it, right?
I guess we can go around here.
But only if the chair wins.
Anything's possible.
There's a Starbucks.
Disney, Miller Monsters.
I'll take care of it.
But if you win.
I'm going to start with you, Moe.
Moe sis.
It's okay to call me Moe-sister.
And, well, honorifics.
From now on, I'll also speak to you in honorifics.
One day a day
Moenesa
One every day.
A good point, a favorite point
Now the music!
Let's start!
“Dancing Sound
Oh, this guy straps moments
história
We are right
All of you are VIPs.
Thank you for your hard work!
Yay!
Shay!
A-ha-ha!
Duh!
What the hell is going on?
A-ha-ha!
Good luck!
Come on.
No, you can't do that.
Ha-ha-ha!
I don't think it's a good idea to play a little music.
Oh, that's right!
Just now.
We were just talking.
The song now?
It's way too much.
I don't know.
I'm not in the mood.
It just came a little late.
I'm sounding like myself right now.
I can't hear you.
It's just... it's... it's just now.
That song you just played...
It wasn't the song I was playing at the Lesson Rehearsal.
I was out of it.
I wasn't in the mood.
A little bit.
I thought it would be a good song for a one-person game,
I wanted to show it one more time.
So, you know, the camera.
There, you see?
Oh, no. Wait a minute.
Okay, then, music.
Let's start!
Kawamura-san did the best.
Atta boy!
Pause, but it's no use.
There's no use in posing.
Thank you!
That's so hot.
Don't get in the car.
I'm feeling a little too much.
What a waste of time!
I didn't get the right one.
Can I have just the right one?
Okay, I'm on it.
Incel, precious.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's great.
BGM.
BGM
Mie-chan already started!
BGM BGM
Why?
BGM
BUN-O-TA
BUN-OTA
Ouchiki!
I can't help it, while I'm doing Ouchie-ki
Ano tatyuu together
Ruler's
Well, okay then.
You can choose
Together
Not too much
Not too much.
I got you just the right one.
Thank you very much.
Music starts.
Music start.
Start!
You mean it's not?
Come on.
There you go.
Of course it's great if you show it now.
That's not what you want to do.
I'm not here for one more time.
I'm not here one more time.
Hey.
Oh, come on!
Oh, not at all.
Not at all
It hurts at all
Does it hurt at all?
Get out of my way.
One more time.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I can't do it.
What's impossible?
What's what?
What?
Here and now, bucky.
I'm feeling a little out of sorts.
You look like a penguin.
Guys, we're a group of four.
It's just the three of us.
So I feel a little bit out of sorts.
I mean, the three of us won the first run and everything.
If we played with four, I might win.
You could win!
Yeah, for sure.
I'll tell them to call you.
You can't win with three.
Um...
I'm not the kind of guy who gets called out by Suzuki.
I'm not the kind of guy who's gonna come when Suzuki calls me.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's go like this now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Look, he's here.
Already here.
Oh, my God.
Okay, come on, circle around.
Go around the top.
From the top.
Can I come in a circle?
You can come in a circle.
Can I be invited to start from the beginning?
We'll play a little game together.
Just a regular game together.
Yes, I'd like to play with everyone.
Yes, ma'am.
Is that normal?
Bail.
There are only three seats.
But now that there are four of us...
It's more like Moeka Suzuki.
It's also just an extension.
It's more like 3 seats.
Three regular members.
That's right.
If we don't do this, we won't have to stop.
Okay, then!
I'll wake up even darker than you.
Even more than you.
Like, I'm going to wake up the darkness, even though we've been working together,
A project to pass on.
It's been a fun project to inherit.
When you finally said it.
I am not yet recognized as an Amera member.
We've been working together for so long.
Research student?
There was an Amerasia research student?
No way.
Today, SENKING will be a problem.
Yes, indeed.
Yes, I'm sure.
I will make it clear today.
I'll keep trying.
I'm just listening, so much ya.
Let's work together.
So, let's start the music.
It's good.
That's good.
It's coming out now.
If we leave now, we'll finish up properly.
We're getting to know each other like in the middle of the country.
A lot.
I know a lot of them.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
You're the one who's not in the picture.
Oh, no.
Yay.
If only I had been so urgent my whole life.
I saw that.
Honestly.
Hey, hey, hey, isn't the content totally different?
You said that Moeika Suzuki didn't reproduce me at all.
Is that right?
Kojima Hana was the official playman of I Blush.
The order of play.
You didn't do that many?
We were working together.
Now I'm curious.
Do that, too. That's what the head of reproduction says.
It's totally different.
Not at all. It's changing all the time.
Nothing fits at all.
Lastly, let's hear from Moeka Suzuki.
Oh, isn't that it?
I've said something in front of the camera.
I've been told by Ms. Suzuki, the center.
Who are the current members?
Well, yes.
I'm Onoka, an Amefurashi student.
I'm not a full member yet.
But I'm sure that by the time we celebrate our 7th or 10th anniversary
I'm sure I'll be a regular member by the time we celebrate our 7th or 10th anniversary.
I hope you all will continue to support me.
I will do my best!
I'll be happy if Chirari appears.
It would be nice if we could get Chirari.
The third line.
Antama! Tatama!
Just started to recreate over the Mire